Hey Lamaday, how are you?
>> I'm good. How you doing?
>> Good. I I guess why Atlanta or
specifically why Atlanta again? What
made this the right fit for you this
year?
>> Um just um a lot of great people, a lot
of good connections here and um you
know, situation wise, I feel like
there's a lot of good things brewing
here in Atlanta and uh I wanted to be a
part of that.
I know you've got some you cross paths
with Ian, but I wonder about Kevin
Stfansky and sort of his offense, how
familiar you are with him in that
system.
>> Uh I mean me me and Kevin went to the
same high school, so we've kind of Yeah.
So we've been uh you know connected in
that way. Um I think the offense is
still kind of being developed right now,
but it's a lot of the similar stuff that
I've done um you know last year and
years previous. So, uh, I think I I'll
fit right in with what's what's being
done.
>> I would imagine you see some opportunity
given the wide receiver room here.
That's got to be one of the factors that
drew you here.
>> Yeah. And I feel like there's
opportunity anywhere. Um, you know, but,
uh, I feel I feel good about being here
in Atlanta.
>> Thanks, Alam.
Justin,
>> you guys are I guess like 15 years apart
in age, but did you how did you know
Kevin through like high school stuff?
Did you just cross paths at all?
>> Uh, yeah. So, uh, we went to the same
high school and it was kind of brought
to my attention,
uh, I think when I was in Philly, um,
that, you know, Kevin actually went to
St. Joe's Prep or maybe even before
then. I think we had played the Browns
before. I I don't know, but somebody
from my high school brought it to my
attention. And then uh you know, I've
played Cleveland last two years, maybe
even three, and uh we've been able to
chat and talk a little bit just like
through passing before the game, after
the game, and stuff like that. So, uh
it's definitely cool to be able to be on
the same team now.
>> Lot of Philly guys obviously, Matt. I
mean, but what is that like kind of
small world feeling to be playing for a
guy to your high school? That's crazy. I
had no idea.
>> It is. It is crazy. And um uh it's just
like you said, small world. So just very
very lucky, very blessed and excited to
get to work with him.
>> And I mean this, you know, free agent
class, there's a lot of guys that that
we're familiar with that Falcons fans
are familiar with like you, like Austin.
I mean, what does that say about this
team about how what you guys are
building um that there are a lot of guys
with familiarity with the organization
that are are returning? Yeah, I think um
you know just trying to get the right
people in the building and to build a a
winning culture and uh you know just
winning games here in Atlanta. That's
you know the main main objective.
>> Any more questions?
>> I got I've got one more Taylor if you
got time.
>> Go ahead.
>> Matt Matt Ryan obviously is you know
Matt Ryan the quarterback. What's your
take on Matt Ryan, president of
football, uh, after a month?
>> Uh, I mean, I don't really have one. Um,
[laughter]
I just know him as a, you know, as a
player, as a person. So, I just know
what he's going to, you know, the type
of attitude and mindset and approach
he's going to bring. Um, but I guess
that's to be determined. I mean, he just
got the got the job.
>> Thanks, Amad. Yeah.
>> Any more questions?
>> Yeah, if I could just throw in one more.
I I got on like 90 seconds late, so if
Josh asked you about this, my apologies,
but how how do you feel like your game
has grown and evolved since last time,
you know, Falcons fans were watching you
wearing red and black?
>> Uh I just feel like it's a lot of like
little details and stuff like that that
I've improved on. Um but I'm still the
same player. Uh I play hard. I'll do
whatever it takes to to get a win. And I
just feel like I can do a lot of things
to help the team win.